Austin Thomas

software developer

Works speak better than words is my idealogy. I am someone who don't give up easily and can solve problems even if it takes a lot of researches. Team or lone, I can be in for both. Meeting deadlines and with clients is something I am never tired of.



austincitesjam19@gmail.com

9384332289

No:59, Siva Sakthi Nagar, Saravanampatti, Coimbatore, INDIA

EDUCATION

BE computer engineering kgisl institute of technology

06/2018 - Present

Twelfth

Lisiuex matric higher sec school

Tenth

Vimal Jyothi convent matric hr sec school

WORK EXPERIENCE

FRESHER

student

FreelancerDigital nirvana

12/2019 – Present

Blogger Independent

06/2019 – Present

SKILLS

PROBLEM SOLVING

SELF-DEVELOPEMENT

ORGANISING

TIME MANAGEMENT

UNDERSTANDING

TEAM WORK

INDEPENDANT

PUBLIC SPEAKING

CONTENT WRITING

CREATIVITY

С

PYTHON

JAVA

JAVASCRIPT

HTML

CSS

SQL

mySQL

PHP

BASH

DEBUGGING

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Whatsapp bot using python

a automated way of engaging with your customers

whatsapp spammer

a fun way of annoying yor loved ones

login webpage using php

- a basic login page designed with HTML,CSS, php and SQL

Voice Calculator

 a simple calculator for the differently abled using pyhton and Google API

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

TAMIL

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

FRENCH

MALAYALAM

Limited Working Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

TECHNOLOGY

AI

INNOVATION

EXPLORING

Future